PROFILE SYNOPSIS

Around six years' experience in Banking and Sales profile through direct Customer interaction.

As a sales manager for the overall success of the organization with primary focus on retains organization relationships & Developing for the organization.

CONTACT

- @ tanubwn86@gmail.com
- +91-9641275361 +91-7699931064
- Rasulpur Paschim; Nimo1; Memari; District-Burdwan, Pin- 713151. West Bengal.

EDUCATION

- NETAJI OPEN UNIVERSITY
 Post Graduate Diploma
 (Journalism & Mass Comm)
 2012
- BURDWAN UNIVERSITY
 Bachelor Of Arts
 2007

TANUSHREE BHATTACHARYA

BANKING & SALES | LIFE, HEALTH, GENERAL INSURANCE & MF EXPERT

OBJECTIVE

Seeking a position that will benefit from my diverse professional experience, flexible and adaptable to work with employees at all levels where my experience can help to improve organization desired goal(s).

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

DEUTSCHE BANK

- Designation: Sales Manager- Advantage Banking (Private & Commercial Clients).
- **Duration:** 2nd April 2018 to till Date.

YES BANK

- **Designation:** Client Relationship Officer.
- **Duration:** 9th February 2016 to 31st March 2018.

BISHALAKSHMI COMMERCIAL (P) LTD. (FRANCHISEE OF M.P. JEWELLERS)

- **Designation:** Customer care Executive (Front Office).
- **Duration:** February 2013 to January 2018.

OTHER QUALIFICATIONS

- Basic knowledge in Computer application program.
- Completed IRDA exam Life, Health & General Insurance.
- Completed AMFI examination- Mutual Fund.

SKILLS



CURRENT PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE DETAILS

DEUTSCHE BANK

KEY RESPONSIBILITIES

- KYC renewal, AML clearance, Incite forex transition through A2 remittance form, SOA Generation, FD advice generation.
- Develop and maintain banking relationships with HNI through individualized customer service.
- Finacle Queries- over the counter transactions (issuance of passbook, Statements, balance enquiry, accounts detail related queries etc).
- Maintain a complete relationship record for assigned customer accounts.
- Cross sells bank products to existing sets of customers.
- Plan and conduct special sales initiatives and events/ campaigns for prospective and existing clients to boost retail liability and TPD business.
- Handling customer's queries (emails, phone calls, Finacle queries etc).
- AOF/ Customer request- KYC/Verification to RPU. Looking after on boarding working in close coordination with the service team.

AWARD & ACHIEVEMENTS

- I had participated in "ELEVATE YOUR GAME" from January 2022 to March 2022 and awarded.
- I had participated in "Shine on" campaign from April 2022 to June 2022 and Qualified.
- Despite the Covid 19 pandemic situation I am a consistent performer for my organization. For my work-excellence, I have received several written appreciations through email.
- Rewarded with special monetary incentive as token of appreciation for "Best Performer-2020" in Kolkata Branch.

- I had participated in "RACE TO WIN" campaign and awarded as winner in JFM 2021.
- Awarded in Health Insurance contest for outstanding performance PAN India in 2020.
- Awarded in Advantage Club contest for outstanding performance PAN India in 2019.
- Awarded in Health Insurance contest for outstanding performance PAN India in 2019.
- Qualified in Monsoon Mania Contest and got rewarded in 2019.

PREVIOUS PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE DETAILS

YES BANK

KEY RESPONSIBILITIES

- SOA Generation, Extending Client Support, Ensure high level customers service orientation and application of the bank.
- Maintain a complete relationship record for assigned customer accounts.
- Ensure high levels of customer service oriented and application of the bank.
- Conduct customer survey campaigns to obtain and review feedback from customers on their level of satisfaction with the bank's product.

AWARD & ACHIEVEMENTS

- Achieved "Spain Mania" contest (Spain Trip) and got awarded by Top Management in Spain. July September' 17.
- Qualified in "Around The World" Contest (Blue Ribbon). Apr June' 17.
- Achieved "London Calling" contest (London Trip) and got awarded by Top Management in London, Jan – March, 17.
- Got an Appreciation Letter from Deodutta Kurane HCM & Mr. Pralay Mandal Senior Group President Retail & Business Banking on 22 November 2016.

BISHALAKSHMI COMMERCIAL (P) LTD. (FRANCHISEE OF M.P. JEWELLERS)

KEY RESPONSIBILITIES

- Handling customer queries in front office.
- Over the counter transaction (handling cash, billing, maintain perches record on daily basis).

EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- Passed Vocal 5th year from Allahabad.
- Learned all type of songs from Kolkata Banichakra Institution.

PERSONAL OTHER DETAILS

- FATHER'S NAME: Sujit Bhattacharya.
- DATE OF BIRTH: 21st of January 1986.
- NATIONALITY: Indian.
- MARITAL STATUS: Single.
- LANGUAGE(S) KNOWN: Bengali, English, Hindi.
- PERSONAL TRAIT: Sincere, Honest and Hard working.

DECLARATION

I hereby	declare	that the	above-n	nentioned	l particulars	are	true to	o the	best	of my	know	ledge	and
believe.													

PLACE:	
DATE:	SIGNATURE